♪ ♪
♪ WELL I JUST HEARD
THE NEWS TODAY ♪
♪ IT SEEMS MY LIFE IS
GOING TO CHANGE ♪
♪ I CLOSED MY EYES,
BEGIN TO PRAY ♪
♪ THEN TEARS OF JOY
STREAM DOWN MY FACE ♪
♪ WITH ARMS WIDE OPEN UNDER
THE SUNLIGHT ♪
♪ WELCOME TO THIS PLACE I'LL
SHOW YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ WITH ARMS WIDE OPEN ♪
♪ WELL I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M READY ♪
♪ TO BE THE MAN I HAVE TO BE ♪
♪ I'LL TAKE A BREATH, I'LL
TAKE HER BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ WE STAND IN AWE,
WE'VE CREATED LIFE ♪
♪ WITH ARMS WIDE OPEN
UNDER THE SUNLIGHT ♪
♪ WELCOME TO THIS PLACE I'LL
SHOW YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ WITH ARMS WIDE OPEN NOW
EVERYTHING HAS CHANGED ♪
♪ I'LL SHOW YOU LOVE, I'LL
SHOW YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ WITH ARMS WIDE OPEN ♪
♪ WIDE OPEN ♪
♪ ♪
♪ IF I HAD JUST ONE WISH
ONLY ONE DEMAND ♪
♪ I HOPE HE'S NOT LIKE ME, I
HOPE HE UNDERSTANDS ♪
♪ THAT HE CAN TAKE THIS LIFE
AND HOLD IT BY THE HAND ♪
♪ AND HE CAN GREET THE WORLD
WITH ARMS WIDE OPEN ♪
♪ WITH ARMS WIDE OPEN
UNDER THE SUNLIGHT ♪
♪ WELCOME TO THIS PLACE I'LL
SHOW YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ WITH ARMS WIDE OPEN NOW
EVERYTHING HAS CHANGEDL ♪
♪ I'LL SHOW YOU LOVE, I'LL
SHOW YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ WITH ARMS WIDE OPEN ♪
♪ ♪